All right,
I'm moving my infantry division...
(Sheldon:)...augmented by a battalion of orcs
from Lord of the Rings.
(Sheldon:)We flank the Tennessee volunteers...
(Sheldon:)...and the North once again
wins the Battle of Gettysburg.
(Howard:)Not so fast. Remember, the South
still has two infantry divisions.
(Howard:)Plus Superman and Godzilla.
(Leonard:)No, no, no. Orcs are magic.
(Leonard:)Superman is vulnerable to magic.
(Leonard:)Not to mention,
you already lost Godzilla...
(Leonard:)...to the Illinois cavalry and Hulk.
(Raj:)Why don't you just have Robert E. Lee
charge the line with Shiva and Ganesh?
(Penny:)- You guys ready to order?
- Hang on.
(Howard:)Shiva and Ganesh?
(Howard:)The Hindu gods
against the entire Union Army?
(Leonard:)And orcs.
(Penny:)I'll be back.
(Raj:)Excuse me. Ganesh is the remover
of obstacles and Shiva's the destroyer.
(Raj:)When the smoke clears,
Lincoln will be speaking Hindi...
(Raj:)...and drinking mint juleps.
My boss says you have to either
order or leave and never come back.
(Howard:)What do you recommend for someone
with a man-sized appetite...
(Howard:)...from a morning of
weight-training and cardio-funk?
(Penny:)A shower.